<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Patch>

<Operation Class="PatchOperationFindMod">
    <mods>
        <li>Science Never Stops: Ambition of the Cosmic</li>
    </mods>
	<match Class="PatchOperationSequence"> 
		<operations>
			<!-- Gen1 Nutrient Bar x5 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Meal_Nutrient_GenI"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Make five nutrient bars made through the further processing of nutrient paste.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<!-- Gen1 Nutrient Bar x25 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Bulk_Meal_Nutrient_GenI"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Make twenty-five nutrient bars made through the further processing of nutrient paste.\n\nNote: Bulk making nutrient bars is 15% faster overall than cooking nutrient bars five times individually, not counting time to collect and transport cooking materials.</description>
				</value>
				
			</li><!-- Gen2 Meal x1 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Meal_Normal_GenII"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Enhance a lavish meal with Abyssal Matter.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<!-- Gen2 Meal x4 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Bulk_Meal_Normal_GenII"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Enhance four lavish meals with Abyssal Matter.\n\nNote: Bulk cooking decadent meals is 15% faster overall than cooking 4 decadent meals individually, not counting time to collect and transport cooking materials.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<!-- Gen2 Nutrient Bar x5 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Meal_Nutrient_GenII"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Make five advanced nutrient bars through the further processing of nutrient paste using Abyssal Alloy and Abyssal Matter.\n\nNote: Advanced nutrient bars have 10% more nutrition value than nutrient paste.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<!-- Gen2 Nutrient Bar x25 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Meal_Bulk_Nutrient_GenII"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Make twenty-five advanced nutrient bars through the further processing of nutrient paste using Abyssal Alloy and Abyssal Matter.\n\nNote 1: Advanced nutrient bars have 10% more nutrition value than nutrient paste.\n\nNote 2: Bulk making advanced nutrient bars is 15% faster overall than cooking nutrient bars five times individually, not counting time to collect and transport cooking materials.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<!-- Gen3 Meal x1 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Meal_Normal_GenIII"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Enhance four decadent meals with Eternal Fabric.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<!-- Gen3 Meal x4 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Bulk_Meal_Normal_GenIII"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Enhance sixteen decadent meals with Eternal Fabric.\n\nNote: Bulk cooking decadent meals is 15% faster overall than cooking 4 decadent meals individually, not counting time to collect and transport cooking materials.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<!-- Gen3 Nutrient Bar x5 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Meal_Nutrient_GenIII"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Make ten luxurious nutrient bars through the further processing of nutrient paste using Eternal Fabric.\n\nNote: Luxurious nutrient bars have 20% more nutrition value than nutrient paste.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<!-- Gen3 Nutrient Bar x25 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Bulk_Meal_Nutrient_GenIII"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Make fifty luxurious nutrient bars through the further processing of nutrient paste using Eternal Fabric.\n\nNote 1: Luxurious nutrient bars have 20% more nutrition value than nutrient paste.\n\nNote 2: Bulk making luxurious nutrient bars is 15% faster overall than cooking luxurious nutrient bars five times individually, not counting time to collect and transport cooking materials.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
		</operations>
	</match>
</Operation>

</Patch>