<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Patch>

<Operation Class="PatchOperationFindMod">
    <mods>
        <li>Science Never Stops: Ambition of the Cosmic</li>
    </mods>
	<match Class="PatchOperationSequence"> 
		<operations>
			<!-- Gen1 Meal x1 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Meal_Normal_GenI"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Cook a luxurious meal from one ingredient. Some ingredients are wasted, but not as many as Lavish meals typically waste.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<!-- Gen1 Meal x4 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Bulk_Meal_Normal_GenI"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Cook four luxurious meals from one ingredient. Some ingredients are wasted, but not as many as Lavish meals typically waste.\n\nNote: Bulk cooking luxurious meals is 15% faster overall than cooking 4 luxurious meals individually, not counting time to collect and transport cooking materials.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<!-- Gen1 Nutrient Bar x5 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Meal_Nutrient_GenI"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Make five nutrient bars from one ingredient. Nutrient bars take a while to prepare, but are more nutrient efficient than even Nutrient Paste.\n\nNote: You effectively get 5 times the food from the same nutrients that would be normally put into making meals.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<!-- Gen1 Nutrient Bar x25 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Bulk_Meal_Nutrient_GenI"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Make twenty-five nutrient bars from one ingredient. Nutrient bars take a while to prepare, but are more nutrient efficient than even Nutrient Paste.\n\nNote: You effectively get 5 times the food from the same nutrients that would be normally put into making meals.\n\nNote: Bulk cooking nutrient bars is 15% faster overall than cooking nutrient bars five times individually, not counting time to collect and transport cooking materials.</description>
				</value>
				
			</li><!-- Gen2 Meal x1 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Meal_Normal_GenII"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Enhance a luxurious or lavish meal with Abyssal Matter.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<!-- Gen2 Meal x4 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Bulk_Meal_Normal_GenII"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Enhance five Nutrient Bars with Cosmic Alloy and Cosmic Matter.\n\nNote: You effectively get 5 times the food from the same nutrients that would be normally put into making meals.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<!-- Gen2 Nutrient Bar x5 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Meal_Nutrient_GenII"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Enhance 25 Nutrient Bars with Abyssal Alloy and Abyssal Matter.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<!-- Gen2 Nutrient Bar x25 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Meal_Bulk_Nutrient_GenII"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Enhance five Nutrient Bars with Abyssal Alloy and Abyssal Matter.\n\nNote: Bulk cooking advanced nutrient bars is 15% faster overall than cooking nutrient bars five times individually, not counting time to collect and transport cooking materials.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<!-- Gen3 Meal x1 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Meal_Normal_GenIII"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Enhance four decadent meals with Eternal Fabric.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<!-- Gen3 Meal x4 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Bulk_Meal_Normal_GenIII"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Enhance sixteen decadent meals with Eternal Fabric..\n\nNote: Bulk cooking decadent meals is 15% faster overall than cooking 4 decadent meals individually, not counting time to collect and transport cooking materials.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<!-- Gen3 Nutrient Bar x5 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Meal_Nutrient_GenIII"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Enhance ten advanced Nutrient Bars with Eternal Fabric.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
			<!-- Gen3 Nutrient Bar x25 -->
			<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
				<xpath>/Defs/RecipeDef[defName="SNS_Recipe_Bulk_Meal_Nutrient_GenIII"]/description</xpath>
				<value>
					<description>Enhance fifty advanced nutrient bars with Eternal Fabric.\n\nNote: Bulk cooking luxurious nutrient bars is 15% faster overall than cooking luxurious nutrient bars five times individually, not counting time to collect and transport cooking materials.</description>
				</value>
			</li>
		</operations>
	</match>
</Operation>

</Patch>